import 'package:quizer/classes/question.dart';

const List<Question> questions = [
  Question(
    question: 'The unicorn is the national animal of Scotland',
    answer: true,
  ),
  Question(
    question: 'A cross between a horse and a zebra is called a \'Hobra\'',
    answer: false,
  ),
  Question(
    question: 'A lion\'s roar can be heard up to eight kilometres away',
    answer: true,
  ),
  Question(
    question: 'Canis lupus is the scientific name for a wolf',
    answer: false,
  ),
  Question(
    question: 'An octopus has three hearts',
    answer: true,
  ),
  Question(
    question: 'Fish cannot blink',
    answer: true,
  ),
  Question(
    question: 'Goldfish have a two second memory',
    answer: false,
  ),
  Question(
    question: 'In Finding Nemo the protagonist is a pufferfish',
    answer: false,
  ),
  Question(
    question: 'The first animal sent into space was a monkey',
    answer: false,
  ),
  Question(
    question: 'In Harry Potter, Draco Malfoy has no siblings',
    answer: true,
  ),
  Question(
    question: 'Walt Disney holds the record for the most Oscars',
    answer: true,
  ),
];
